Welcome back to the Amanda Seals show. I'm Amanda Seals. Now, Nails, I know that the barbers,
there's a whole thing that's been happening lately with the barbers. Barbers been charging
a little bit more for the haircuts these days, right? Is this true?
Yep. Yep. Inflation prices.
So, you know, the same thing has been happening with the braids. Now, I've been seeing rumblings
of this on the internet where people are like, yo, like these hairstylists is wilding. You know,
they're charging you if you come 10 minutes late. They're giving you extra fees if they want to
if you have to have hair washed, et cetera, et cetera. And I had never experienced it myself
until I wanted my sister. Well, my sister wanted to get her hair braided because she is about to
have a baby and she doesn't want to have to worry about her hair when she has the baby. So I was
like, all right, well, I'll pay for you to get your hair braided. Y'all, the braiders, are y'all ready?
The braiders cost me $675. $675. And I just feel like that's an exorbitant price.
Am I bugging? Am I bugging y'all? Please. Because I get my hair in twists and it ain't
even nothing close to that, but I would love to hear from you guys. And I want to know like
from the braiders as well, like why has the price like gone up? Why have, why have we fat
joed the price of braiding? Yesterday's price is not today's price. Please share with me. 1-855-262-6328.
1-855-AMANDA-A. Can you hear my eyebrows? They're touching because they're so confused.